Prad Lamichhane

Data Analyst | Sydney, NSW https://www.linkedin.com/in/prad-lamichhane-072b6a28b/https://github.com/Prad111

Profile

With a knack for telling compelling stories through Data, I bring experience engaging with stakeholders, through a year in customer service, four years in Aged Care, three years as a Business Owner managing a family business, and five years as a Loan Officer. An eager learner, I use my transferable skills gained, combined with the technical and soft-skills learned during a 13-weeks Data Analytics bootcamp to further my Data Analytical skills to invest into my future organisation.

Skills

Technical	Skills
------------------	--------

- Python
- SQL
- PowerBI
- Git
- Shell
- Agile

Soft Skills

- Time Management
- People Management
- Ability to work in a team
- Growth Mindset
- Persistence and Resilience
- Excellent Communication Skills with self-motivation

Experience

Graduate, Data Analytics Bootcamp

July 2023- Oct 2023 Generation Australia

- Hands-on experience using Python, SQL and PowerBI while utilising exceptional attention-to-detail to analyse and visualise data.
- Program consisted of a combination of self-driven, independent work and collaborative team-work.
- Utilised strong problem-solving and analytical skills to solve complex business problems and provide solutions for projects and course-work.

Bus Operator

Sept 2022 - July 2023 Busways, Glendenning, NSW

- Developed excellent communication skills and attention to details.
- Served more than 500 passengers a day with more than 90% customer satisfaction score.

Managed Family-owned Dairy Business

Aug 2019 - Aug 2022 Kathmandu, Nepal

- Coordinated with all the stake-holders to make quality dairy products available to consumers during disruption caused by Covid-19.
- Managed all aspects of the dairy business leading to an increase of net-profit by 50% within 3
 years.

Admin Officer

Feb 2015 - July 2019 Zion Lutheran Aged Care, Brisbane, QLD

- Developed attention to detail by Completing behavioural documentations, and by rostering.
- Developed team skills by liaising with team members, health professionals and external agencies.

Loan Officer

Feb 2008- Dec 2013 Standard Chartered Bank, Nepal

- Started with selling various consumer loan products to customers.
- Managed close relationships with external parties such as car dealers, property developers, and large employers to ensure steady flow of customers for loan products.
- Became the highest seller of customer loan products in the bank in 2009.
- Moved into assessing and approving consumer loan applications equivalent to Au\$ 500,000.
- Used attention to detail and research skills to approve loans. Had a default rate of less than 0.1%, one of the best in the bank.

Education

Oct 2023 Generation Australia, Sydney, Bootcamp on Data Analytics

Feb 2015 Griffith University, Brisbane, QLD Graduate Diploma in Business

Dec 2007 Tribhuvan University, Nepal Bachelor of Business

Languages

English, Nepali and Hindi

References

References available upon request